siliconrepublic.com 2018-12-30

# Privacy Policy | Silicon Republic

Silicon Republic respects your right to privacy. We do not collect or store personal information when you visit our websites, Siliconrepublic.com and [Inspirefest.com](https://inspirefest.com/).

This Cookie Policy outlines our policy concerning the use of cookies and similar technologies.

We may update our Cookie Policy from time to time to reflect any changes in technology or legislation, or our data-use policies, which may affect the way in which cookies and similar technologies are used by us and how you, as a user, can manage them.

## **What are cookies and how do we use them?**

Cookies are small text files placed in your computer, tablet, mobile or other device. We use cookies to collect non-identifiable data to generate aggregated data reports, which help us to improve our website, user experience, content and event promotions, and to verify our audience figures to sponsor and partners.

## **The information we collect and share**

We use aggregated data to understand how visitors discover and navigate our site, such as:

  * Clickstream data, which shows visitor traffic around our websites (for example: pages accessed, topics viewed, time on page, videos watched, outbound links clicked, social media shares and our most popular content and topics)
  * The country and city where our users are located
  * How users arrived at our sites, including which social network or platform referred them

This information is used only to verify our audience profile and none of this data will be used to identify individual site visitors unless we are required to do so by law.

None of the cookies we set on our site collect or store any personal information and we only share aggregated data with approved advertisers and partners.

## **Your choices**

More information about cookies and details of how to manage or disable them can be found on [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/).

If you wish to opt out of being retargeted via display and search ads, and/or advertised to via cookies’ tracking, [Your Ad Choices](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/ie/your-ad-choices) from the [Digital Advertising Alliance](https://youradchoices.com/about) (DAA) can help you control your information flow at a browser level (ie these settings will apply to all sites you visit in your browser). All accredited ad agencies and platforms participating in the DAA are expected to respect restrictions enacted here.

Your device or browser may also enable you to control the collection of your data. Check your device or browser instructions for more information in this respect.

## **What we do when you submit your email address**

If you volunteer personal information in an email or in the form of a newsletter subscription, enquiry or comment, the data will not be made available to any third party and will be used solely for the purpose for which it was intended.

We use [MailChimp](http://www.mailchimp.com/) to help us deliver email marketing communications. MailChimp has the [TRUSTe Privacy Seal](https://www.trustarc.com/privacy-certification-standards/). TRUSTe is an independent third party that operates a globally recognised privacy trustmark. Please read [MailChimp’s privacy policy](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/) for more information as you agree to this, and the transfer of your information to MailChimp, when you sign up to marketing communications from us.

## **The cookies we use**

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google. This service uses cookies to help Silicon Republic analyse how visitors use and access its websites. The information generated about your use of the website will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of our websites, compiling reports on website activity for Siliconrepublic.com and Inspirefest.com, and providing other services relating to our website activity and internet usage.

For an added level of user privacy, we have enabled IP address anonymisation. With this enabled, Google Analytics anonymises the address as soon as technically feasible at the earliest possible stage of the collection network. This system has been designed to avoid storage of a full IP address.

You can find out how Google uses information from sites that use Google Analytics [here](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). Further information on Google Analytics, including how to opt out, is available via the [Google Analytics Help Centre](http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html).

Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google.

You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser. However, please note that if you do this, you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website.

By using this website and allowing cookies to remain enabled, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.

## In addition to cookies set by Google Analytics, the following cookies are also used by Silicon Republic:

##### **Google AdWords cookies**

We use these cookies for the sole purpose of promoting and marketing our events, awards and campaigns.

Google AdWords cookies remember that you have visited Siliconrepublic.com or Inspirefest.com. This information is shared with Google AdWords and we may use third parties to send you ads on our behalf after you leave our website. These ads will only be for services provided by Silicon Republic, such as promoting events and offers for our annual Inspirefest event.

##### **Event-based cookies**

These are cookies set by approved third parties to enable you to book events on embedded forms on our sites, such as ticket booking for Inspirefest.com.

We also use [Google Tag Manager](https://www.google.com/analytics/tag-manager/) to collect non-identifiable data on links clicked and videos played, which we use to monitor audience engagement and interest in companies and topics.

##### **Other third-party cookies**

Some cookies etc on our websites are not related to Siliconrepublic.com or Inspirefest.com. When you visit a page with content embedded from, for example, YouTube or Facebook, or social media widgets such as the Twitter share button, these service providers may use their own cookies.

We do not control the use of these cookies as they can only be accessed by the party that originally set them. You should check the third-party websites for more information about these cookies.

## **What we share with advertisers, partners and sponsors**

We only ever share aggregated data on audience behaviour and do not share personally identifiable information with our advertisers, partners and sponsors.

We only carry advertisements from trusted partners and/or their agents. We do not carry advertisements from ad exchanges or advertising networks.

Some advertisers may use advertisements containing cookies that we do not control. We ensure that all ads on Siliconrepublic.com are delivered though [DoubleClick](https://www.doubleclickbygoogle.com/) with non-personalised ad targeting enabled, which means ads served are not based on a user’s past behaviour. You can learn more about non-personalised ads [here](https://support.google.com/dfp_premium/answer/9005435).

## **Contacting the website**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement or the security practices of this site, please email [webmaster@siliconrepublic.com](mailto:webmaster@siliconrepublic.com) or submit your query in writing to Silicon Republic Knowledge & Events Management Ltd, Digital Exchange, Crane Street, Dublin 8, Ireland.

**Updated: 24 May 2018**

[_Padlock image_](http://www.shutterstock.com/pic-219342559/stock-photo-pair-of-locked-padlocks-on-the-bridge-as-a-symbol-of-eternal-love-romance-marriage-shallow-depth.html) _by_[ _Photosebia_](http://www.shutterstock.com/gallery-594583p1.html) _via Shutterstock_
